Guide to the Johan Kugelberg hip hop collection, circa 1975-1985, 2008.
Kugelberg, Johan hip hop collection,
- Series I. Sound Recordings (1-24)
  - LPs - SR 574-623 (Box 12)
    - Ain't no thing / Steinski Say Ho! / J Rocc Performed by: J Rocc, 2004; SR-605 (Box 12)
      Track listing: Ain't no thing (Steinski messin' around) / Steinski -- Say Ho! / J. Rocc.
    - Space is the place / the Jonzun Crew Performed by: Jonzun Crew, ca. 1985; SR-606 (Box 12)
      Track listing: Space is the place (vocal) -- Space is the place (instrumental)
    - Pack jam / the Jonzun Crew Performed by: Jonzun Crew, ca. 1985; SR-607 (Box 12)
      Track listing: Pack jam (Look out for the OVC) (vocal) -- Pack jam (Look out for the OVC) (instrumental)
    - Rappin' Rodney Performed by: Rodney Dangerfield; with instrumental acc, 1983; SR-608 (Box 12)
      Track listing: Rappin' Rodney -- Rappin' Rodney (instrumental).
    - Rap Master Ronnie / Composed by GB Trudeau, E Swados Performed by: Reathel Bean and the Doonesbury Break Crew. (Garry B. Trudeau and Elizabeth Swados), 1984; SR-609 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Silver Screen
      Track listing: Rap Master Ronnie (short version) -- Rap Master Ronnie (long version) -- Rap Master Ronnie.
    - Rock the house: part 1-2 Performed by: Danny "K"., Mix by Special G, ca. 1985; SR-610 (Box 12)
      Publisher: T.D. Records Inc.
    - Zodiac rhymes: pt 1-2 / Disco Daddy Performed by: Disco Daddy, 1983; SR-611 (Box 12)
      Publisher: California Gold
    - Sally & Dee Performed by: Sir Fresh, D.J.: Critical, 1985; SR-612 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Ultra Records
      Track listing: Sally & Dee -- Sally & Dee (instrumental)
    - We're # 1 / Team Performed by: Team, 1981; SR-613 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Rouge Record; Ville St. Laurent Que.: Manufactured by Unidisc Records
      Track listing: We're # 1-- We're # 1 (instrumental)
    - General hospi-tale / H King and L Tedesco Performed by: Afternoon Delights, 1981; SR-614 (Box 12)
      Track listing: General hospi-tale -- General hospi-tale (instrumental).
    - Get the party jumpin / Solo Sound Performed by: Solo Sound, 1981; SR-615 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Express Records: Distributed by Forward Records
      Track listing: Get the party jumpin -- Get the party jumpin--part 2.
    - Father Goose; Father Goose II Performed by: M. Brathwaite, W. Carter, 1980; SR-616 (Box 12)
      Publisher: We-Four Records
      Track listing: Father Goose (the ball at Oz-- ) -- Father Goose II (the ball at Oz-- ) (instrumental).
    - Lookin' good (shake your body) Performed by: Eddie Cheba, vocals; with instrumental ensemble, 1979; SR-617 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Treeline
      Track listing: Lookin' good (shake your body): vocal -- Lookin' good (shake your body): instrumental.
    - School days; Out of school Performed by: Mr. JC, 1982; SR-618 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Drum Beat
      Track listing: School days -- Out of school.
    - Valley style / T Ski Valley Performed by: T Ski Valley, ca. 1975; SR-619 (Box 12)
      Track listing: Valley style -- Valley style (dub mix)
    - Blue jeans / Smash Performed by: Smash, ca. 1985; SR-620 (Box 12)
      Publisher: DTD Records
    - Fresh Avenue / Diamond "D" Performed by: Diamond "D"; written, produced and arranged by Spyder-D, 1984; SR-621 (Box 12)
      Track listing: Fresh Avenue (vocal) -- Fresh Avenue (bonus mix) -- Fresh Avenue (instrumental)
    - Election 80 rapp / The Unknown Rapper Performed by: Unknown Rapper, 1980; SR-622 (Box 12)
      Track listing: Election 80 rapp -- Election 80 rapp (instrumental)
    - Shout - shake / Billy Lamont & Company Performed by: Billy Lamont, 1980; SR-623 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Glow Hill Records
      Track listing: Shout - shake (vocal-short version, vocal-long version) -- Shout - shake (instrumental-long version)
  - LPs - SR 624-676 (Box 13)
    - Battmann, let Mo-Jo handle it / Mo-Jo Performed by: Mojo, 1982; SR-624 (Box 13)
      Track listing: Battmann: Let Mo-Jo handle it -- Battmann: Let Mo-Jo handle it (instrumental)
    - Rhyme master Mr. Spice & The Chosen Few Performed by: Mr. Spice & the Chosen Few, ca. 1985; SR-625 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Sharp Records
      Track listing: No crack -- Masters of rap -- Learn to be an emcee -- Torture beat.
    - Super rock body shock / Eye Beta Rock, featuring Dr. Groove Performed by: Eye Beta Rock, ca. 1985; SR-626 (Box 13)
      Publisher: H.E.R.O. Records
      Track listing: Super rock body shock -- Super rock body shock (edited version).
    - Sex machine / Fat Boys Performed by: Fat Boys, 1986; SR-627 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Sonet Records
      Track listing: Sex machine -- Sex machine (dub version) -- Beat box is rockin'.
    - Rock ruling / Fat Boys Performed by: Fat Boys, 1987; SR-628 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Tin Pan Apple: Polygram Records
      Track listing: Rock ruling (imperial version) -- Rock ruling (royale version) -- Hell, no! (Parents' version) -- Hell, no! (bad kids' dub).
    - Falling in love (extended mix); Protect yourself/My nuts (medley); Falling in love (dubb) / Fat Boys Performed by: Fat Boys, 1987; SR-629 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Urban: PolyGram
    - Lie-Z (12" lie); Lie-Z (7" lie); On and on (12") -- On and on (7") / Fat Boys Performed by: Fat Boys, 1989; SR-630 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Tin Pan Apple: Polydor
    - Crushin' Performed by: Fat Boys, 1987; SR-631 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Tin Pan Apple; marketed by Polygram Records
      Track listing: Crushin' -- Protect yourself/my nuts -- Rock ruling -- Making noise -- Boys will be boys -- Falling in love -- Fat Boys dance -- Wipeout -- Between the sheets -- Hell no!
    - Obsession; Obsession (version scratch); Obsession (version a cappella [sic]) Performed by: Franc¸ois Feldman, vocals; with acc., 1984; SR-632 (Box 13)
    - Flamethrower rap / Seth Justman Performed by: Felix & Jarvis, 1982; SR-633 (Box 13)
      Publisher: RFC Records
      Track listing: Flamethrower rap: long version -- Flamethrower rap: short version -- Flamethrower rap: instrumental version.
    - Wild and crazzy song; Funk's gone crazy / Fenderella Performed by: Fenderella, vocals; with acc. (Joyce Irby), 1980; SR-634 (Box 13)
    - 1980 / Flakes I Performed by: Flakes I, 1980; SR-635 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Magic Disc Records
      Track listing: Flakes rap -- Sugar frosted lover -- Hey there lonely girl -- Miss fine lover -- No one )can love you like I do) -- Dance (don't cha wanna) -- Your love's to [sic] strong for me -- Flakes reprise.
    - Tender love Performed by: Force M.D.'s, 1985; SR-636 (Box 13)
      Track listing: Tender love (extended vocal remix) -- Tender love (extended instrumental remix).
    - Double Dutch II Performed by: Frankie Smith, 1982; SR-637 (Box 13)
      Track listing: Double Dutch II: the rope -- Double Dutch II (instrumental).
    - Auction / Frankie Smith Performed by: Frankie Smith, 1981; SR-638 (Box 13)
      Track listing: The auction -- The auction (instrumental).
    - Double dutch bus Performed by: Frankie Smith, vocals; with instrumental acc, 1980; SR-639 (Box 13)
    - Jeckyll and Hyde dance: Doing the do / Dr. Jeckyll and Mr. Hyde Performed by: Dr. Jeckyll & Mr. Hyde, ca. 1985; SR-640 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Rojac
    - Respect; Respect (instrumental) / Dr. John Blair Performed by: John Blair, 1983; SR-641 (Box 13)
      Publisher: 3C Records
    - Do the Roxanne (dance) part one; Do the Roxanne (dance) part two: dub version Performed by: Doctor Rocx and Co, 1985; SR-642 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Slice Records
    - Davy DMX Performed by: Davy DMX, 1984; SR-643 (Box 13)
      Track listing: One for the treble (fresh) (vocal mix) -- One for the treble (fresh) (instrumental) -- Bonus beats.
    - In the cabbage patch Performed by: Delmar Donnell; with background singers and musicians, 1984; SR-644 (Box 13)
    - D.J. Hollywood Performed by: D.J. Hollywood, ca. 1985; SR-645 (Box 13)
    - Bite it Performed by: Drum, 1984; SR-646 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Jamar Records
      Track listing: Bite it -- Bite it (instrumental)
    - Doug E Fresh & the Get Fresh Crew Performed by: Doug E. Fresh, 1988; SR-647 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Reality: Distributed by Danya Records
    - Show (vocal); The show; La-di-da-di; The show (instrumental) Performed by: Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew (side A); Doug E. Fresh and M.C. Ricky D. (side B), 1985; SR-648 (Box 13)
    - Freak-a-holic: (re-mix) / Egyptian Lover Performed by: Egyptian Lover, 1984; SR-649 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Egyptian
      Track listing: Freak-a-holic (12 inch long version) -- Freak-a-holic (radio version) -- Livin' on the Nile (extended club re-mix).
    - Alezby Inn; Sexy style Performed by: Egyptian Lover, ca. 1985; SR-650 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Egyptian Empire
      Track listing: The Alzeby Inn (remodeled version) -- The Alezby Inn (vocal vacancy) -- Sexy style (sexy ain't it).
    - Rock Performed by: East Coast, vocal and instrumental ensemble, 1978; SR-651 (Box 13)
      Publisher: RSO
    - Kim Performed by: Dynamic Breakers, 1985; SR-652 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Sunnyview
      Track listing: Kim -- Kim (dub version).
    - Freakman / Empire (Projecting Penny) Performed by: Empire, 1981; SR-653 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Quality: RFC Records
    - Knock him out, Sugar Ray; EU Freeze / Experience Unlimited Performed by: Experience Unlimited, 1980; SR-654 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Vermack Records
    - Sale histoire / Fab 5 Freddy Performed by: Fab 5 Freddy, 1982; SR-655 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Disc' AZ International
      Track listing: Une sale histoire (female version) -- Une sale histoire (male version).
    - Rap attack / Family Four Performed by: Family Four, ca. 1980; SR-656 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Tyson Records
      Track listing: Rap attack -- Rap attack.
    - R-trax; D-rail / Knight Action Performed by: Knight Action, 1985; SR-657 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Let's Dance
      Track listing: R-trax (special mix) -- D-rail (special mix).
    - B boys style / Lil' Jazzy Jay & Cool Supreme Performed by: Lil' Jazzy Jay & Cool Supreme; background vocals by Cyré, 1985; SR-658 (Box 13)
      Track listing: B boys style (club vocal) -- B boys style (dub instrumental) -- B boys style (radio edit).
    - House rocker / Lovebug Starski Performed by: Lovebug Starski, vocals; with instrumental and vocal acc, 1986; SR-659 (Box 13)
      Track listing: House rocker -- Positive life -- Baby tell me -- Amityville (The house on the hill) -- Saturday night -- Say what you wanna say -- Eighth wonder.
    - To the boys in the band; Roller shake / la Flavour Performed by: Flavour, 1980; SR-660 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Sweet City
      Track listing: To the boys in the band -- Roller shake.
    - Boogie to the bop / Mantus & Omega 88 Performed by: Mantus & Omega 88; hot shot remix by Aldo Marin, 1983; SR-661 (Box 13)
      Publisher: SMI
      Track listing: Boogie to the bop -- Boogie to the bop (original version) -- Boogie bonus beats.
    - Beat biter; The bridge; Dub biter / MC Shan Performed by: M.C. Shan, 1986; SR-662 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Bridge Records
      Track listing: Beat biter (radio mix) -- Beat biter (extended mix) -- The bridge -- Dub biter.
    - Disco dream / the Mean Machine Performed by: Mean Machine, 1981; SR-663 (Box 13)
      Track listing: Disco dream (vocal) -- Disco dream (instrumental).
    - Dr. Jam (in the slam) / Men at Play Performed by: Men at Play, 1983; SR-664 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Sunshine Recordings
      Track listing: Dr. Jam (in the slam) (long version) -- Dr. Jam (in the slam) (short version) -- Dr. Jam instrumental.
    - Whip rap; Let it whip / Disco Four Performed by: Disco Four, 1982; SR-665 (Box 13)
      Track listing: Whip rap -- Let it whip (instrumental).
    - Changes (we go through); Do or die Bed Sty; Changes (dub dub) / Divine Sounds Performed by: Divine Sounds, 1984; SR-666 (Box 13)
      Track listing: Changes (we go through) -- Changes (we go through) (short version) -- Do or die Bed Sty -- Changes (dub dub).
    - Rhythm rap rock / Count Coolout Performed by: Count Coolout, 1980; SR-667 (Box 13)
      Track listing: Rhythm rap rock (w/ vocal rap) -- Rhythm rap rock (instrumental).
    - Here to stay (me and my double RR) / Count Coolout Performed by: Count Coolout, 1981; SR-668 (Box 13)
      Track listing: Here to stay (me and my double R.R.) -- Here to stay (me and my double R.R.) (instrumental).
    - We are known as emcees (we turn party's out) / Crash Crew Performed by: Crash Crew, 1983; SR-669 (Box 13)
      Track listing: We are known as emcees (we turn party's out) (vocal) -- We are known as emcees (we turn party's out) (instrumental).
    - Music ain't loud e-nuf / D.J. Kool Performed by: D.J. Kool, 1988; SR-670 (Box 13)
      Track listing: The music ain't loud e-nuf (radio edit) -- The music ain't loud e-nuf (dub mix) -- The music ain't loud e-nuf (D.C. mix) -- The music ain't loud e-nuf (N.Y. mix).
    - Challenge / Dr. Jeckyll & Mr. Hyde Performed by: Dr. Jeckyll & Mr. Hyde, 1982; SR-671 (Box 13)
      Track listing: The challenge -- The challenge (instrumental).
    - Do what you wanna do Performed by: Tony Cook and Party People, 1982; SR-672 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Half Moon Productions
    - Drum machine Performed by: Drum Machine (J. Burnett, F. Finley, C. Rote), 1982; SR-673 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Jayco Records
      Track listing: Drum machine (vocal) -- Drum machine (instrumental)
    - Moving up / Sargeant & Malone Performed by: Sargeant & Malone (S. Sargeant and D. Malone), 1981; SR-674 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Half Moon
      Track listing: Moving up -- Moving up (instrumental)
    - Bongo rock; Apache Performed by: Apache Band, ca. 1975; SR-675 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Guava Records
    - Ling ching tong / Joe Bataan Performed by: Joe Bataan, lead vocals; with instrumental and vocal acc, 1981; SR-676 (Box 13)
      Publisher: Salsoul
      Track listing: Ling ching tong (4:56) -- Ling ching tong (instrumental) (5:10).
  - LPs - SR 677-723 (Box 14)
    - Party night (rap it up); Party night (instrumental) Performed by: Johnnie & Michael Hill, ca. 1980; SR-677 (Box 14)
    - Shut-up (Rules of the game) Performed by: Juny Boom, 1981; SR-678 (Box 14)
      Track listing: Shut-up (Rules of the game) (rap) -- Shut-up (Rules of the game) (instrumental)
    - Get outta my face / Ken "C" Performed by: Ken C, 1983; SR-679 (Box 14)
      Track listing: Get outta my face (vocal) -- Get outta my face (instrumental)
    - City slicker / J Blackfoot Performed by: J. Blackfoot, 1983; SR-680 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Sound Town Records
      Track listing: The way of the city -- Taxi -- Street girl -- One of those parties -- Where is love -- I stood on the sidewalk and cried -- City slicker -- All because of what you did to me last night -- Can you hang.
    - Get on up Performed by: Jazzy Dee, vocals and guitar; with instrumental acc, 1983; SR-681 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Laurie Records
      Track listing: Get on up (vocal) -- Get on up (instrumental).
    - Superappin'; Superappin' theme / Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five Performed by: Grandmaster Flash, 1979; SR-682 (Box 14)
    - That's the joint / Funky 4 plus 1 Performed by: Funky 4 plus 1, 1980; SR-683 (Box 14)
      Track listing: That's the joint (vocal) -- That's the joint (instrumental).
    - Rappin and rocking the house Performed by: Funky Four Plus One More, 1979; SR-684 (Box 14)
      Track listing: Rappin and rocking the house (version "A") -- Rappin and rocking the house (version "B").
    - Disco mix / Fusion Performed by: Fusion, ca. 1975; SR-685 (Box 14)
    - State of shock rapp / Future Flash; King MC; "Erotic" rapp / The Future MC's Performed by: Future Flash, King M.C., and The Future M.C.'s, ac. 1980; SR-686 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Hitt's Records
    - Rappin', dancin', and laughin' / Blow Fly Performed by: Blow Fly; with vocal and instrumental acc, 1980; SR-687 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Weird World Records
      Track listing: Convoy -- Blowfly vs. Darth Vadar -- Cricka -- The incredible fulk -- The word game -- The insects theme.
    - Reflections / Iceberg Slim Performed by: Iceberg Slim; background music, Red Holloway Quartet, 1976; SR-688 (Box 14)
      Track listing: The fall -- Broadway Sam -- Durealla -- Mama debt.
    - Back door daddy Performed by: Skillet, Leroy & Lawanda, 1972; SR-689 (Box 14)
      Track listing: He got away -- Slack jawed Leroy -- Insect ball -- Too tight -- Clap Trap Johnson -- Republicans 23rd psalm -- The boss -- Bart & Fay -- Valley of Death -- Heavy hip woman -- Back door daddy.
    - From the roots came the rapper / Joe Tex Performed by: Joe Tex, 1972; SR-690 (Box 14)
      Track listing: Lovin' man -- The only way I know how to love you -- I can do it better -- Chained in the mind -- I'll never fall in love again -- Oh me oh my (I'm a fool for you baby) -- There's no business like love -- The baby is mine -- Somethings in life are worth dying for -- Hate yourself in the morning.
    - Last Poets Performed by: Last Poets, with percussion acc, ca. 1975; SR-691 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Douglas Recording Corp.
      Track listing: Run, nigger. -- On the subway. -- Niggers are scared of revolution. -- Black thighs. -- Gashman. -- Wake up, niggers. -- New York, New York. -- Jones comin' down. -- When the revolution comes. -- Just because. -- Black wish. -- Two little boys. -- Surprises.
    - God is for real, man Performed by: Carl F. Burke, 1960; SR-692 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Rejoice Records
    - Call-and-response; Rhythmic group singing Performed by: Ella Jenkins and a group of school children with instruments, 1957; SR-693 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Scholastic Records
      Track listing: Ta-boo -- Zeembah -- Moon don't go -- Moon don't go (with instruments) -- Toom-bah-ee-lero -- Toom-bah-ee-lero (with instruments) -- A chant from West Africa -- A love chant from North Africa -- An American chain gang chant -- An Arabic chant that means "Welcome"
    - Ray Scott live Performed by: Ray Scott, 1975; SR-694 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Elka Productions
      Track listing: Introduction -- I am what I am -- Not in -- Mattresses for mice -- Knee grows -- Black girls-white girl -- Nigga say -- Hypertension -- I got ta whisper -- Bitch -- I like freaks (peep freaks) -- Mr. Heroin -- Rich nigga -- Hillbillies' love affair -- M.G.M.-Mills grocery market -- High school -- Superstitions -- Cocaine (One n' one) -- Mr. Heroin [sic] -- Stop smokin in five days -- Buck-teeth -- Love thy neighbor
    - Prayer / Ray Scott Performed by: Ray Scott (i.e. Walter Spriggs), 1971; SR-695 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Checker
    - "The sermon" by Rev Give-a-Dam: I ain't lying / Tommy Brown Performed by: Tommy Brown, vocals, with accompaniment, 195ca. 1955; SR-696 (Box 14)
      Publisher: T and L Productions
      Track listing: I ain't lying -- Hymn #1: Right time is the night time -- Hymn #2: Weeping and crying
    - Has Hell made reservations for you? Performed by: Nancy Spearman and Geraldine Johnson, 195ca. 1955; SR-697 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Ambassador Gospel Record Co.
      Track listing: Sermon no. 1 -- Sermon no. 2
    - Butterbeans and Susie Performed by: Butterbeans & Susie, with musical acc, 195ca. 1955; SR-698 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Festival Records
      Track listing: Ballin' the jack (2:03) -- Get yourself a monkey man (2:57) -- There''ll be some changes made (2:39) -- Construction gang (3:07) -- I've got the blues for home sweet home (3:35) -- A married man's a fool (2:36) -- When my man shimmies (2:25) -- Deal yourself another hand (2:31) -- Street piano (2:40) -- Until the real thing comes along (5:25).
    - Here comes the judge / Shorty Long Performed by: Shorty Long, vocals; with instrumental ensemble, 1968; SR-699 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Soul
      Track listing: Here comes the judge (2 min., 37 sec.) -- Night fo' last (Vocal) (2 min., 34 sec.) -- Function at the Junction (2 min., 56 sec.) -- Don't mess with my weekend (2 min., 27 sec.) -- Ain't no justice (2 min., 58 sec.) -- Devil with the blue dress -- Night 'fo last (Vocal) (2 min., 34 sec.) -- Stranded in the jungle (2 min., 57 sec.) -- Here comes fat Albert (2 min., 48 sec.) -- Sing what you wanna (2 min., 21 sec.) -- Another hurt like this (2 min., 58 sec.) -- People sure act funny (2 min., 6 sec.).
    - Urban Holiness Service Performed by: Elder Charles D. Beck, conductor; with vocal and instrumental service music, 1957; SR-700 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Folkways
      Track listing: Statement by Elder Beck -- Don't You See -- Drive Old Satan Away, Lord -- Walk in the Night -- Job statement by David Beck -- Let the Church Say Amen -- I Know the Lord: He Laid His Hand On Me -- Search Me Lord -- I'm a Soldier -- Satisfied.
    - Huey! Black Panther platform with Seale, Cleaver, Rap Brown Performed by: Bobby Seale, Eldridge Cleaver, H. Rap Brown, 1972; SR-701 (Box 14)
    - Funkadelic / Funkadelic Performed by: Funkadelic (Ed Hazel, lead guitar, vocals; Bill Nelson, bass, vocals; Tawl Ross, guitar; Tiki Fullwood, drums, vocals; Mickey Atkins, organ), 1970; SR-702 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Westbound
      Track listing: Mommy, what's a Funkadelic? -- I bet you -- Music for my mother -- I got a thing, you got a thing, everybody's got a thing -- Good old music -- Qualify & satisfy -- What is soul.
    - Free from sin Performed by: Prince Far I, 1979; SR-703 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Trojan Records
      Track listing: Free from sin -- When jay ready you got to move -- Call on I in trouble -- Don't deal with folly -- Light of fire -- Reggae music -- Go home on the morning train -- Siren -- I and I are the chosen one.
    - Tramp time, [vol. 1] / Jimmy Lynch Performed by: Isaac "Jimmy" Lynch, 1961; SR-704 (Box 14)
      Publisher: La Val
      Track listing: Tramp time -- I got you, I feel good -- Tramp time
    - Pillow talk / Sylvia Robinson Performed by: Sylvia Robinson, vocals & guitar with instrumental ensemble, 1973; SR-705 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Vibration
      Track listing: Pillow talk -- Give it up in vain -- Sunday -- Don't leave me starving -- My thing -- Didn't I -- Had any lately -- Not on the outside -- Cowards way out.
    - Big Ben sings Performed by: Scat Man Crothers, 1973; SR-706 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Motown
      Track listing: I'm the melody man -- Elaine, Elaine -- I found someone -- God bless the child -- Nobody knows why -- Dead man's blues -- Waiting for my baby -- How long, how long blues -- Kansas City -- Tell me how long the train's been gone -- Wondering -- (It will have to do) until the real thing comes along -- Hey Lawdy Mama.
    - Blowfly's freak party Performed by: Blowfly, 1987; SR-707 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Oops!
      Track listing: Blowfly's freak party -- Fuck & suck train -- Fuck the fat off -- Fuck like a zombie -- Fuck wars -- Latin pussy slam -- Safari -- No business like fuck business -- Cum of a lifetime
    - Guess who's coming home: Black fighting men recorded live in Vietnam Performed by: Wallace Terry, 1972; SR-708 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Black Forum
    - Rock 'n roll with "Scat Man" Crothers Performed by: Scat Man Crothers, vocals with jazz sextet, 1956; SR-709 (Box 14)
      Publisher: Tops
      Track listing: Ghost riders in the sky -- Exactly like you -- September song -- Nobody knows why -- St. James Infirmary -- My blue heaven -- I'm gonna sit right down and write myself a letter -- I got rhythm -- The best things in life are free -- The gal looks good -- Please don't talk about me when I'm gone -- Baby, won't you please come home.
    - Soul brothers in heaven and hell / Tommy Brown Performed by: Tommy Brown, 1960; SR-710 (Box 14)
      Publisher: T & L Productions